# GRAHAM HARRIS

#### CONTACT

929.244.0668 grahamh1019@gmail.com Brooklyn, NY

#### **EDUCATION**

New York University, Sept. 2018 – May 2022 GPA: 3.6 Major in Computer Science Minors in Mathematics and Italian

#### **LINKS**

<u>GitHub</u> LinkedIn

Resume Website

### **SKILLS**

- Scrum/Agile
- Project Management
- Data Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Low/No Code Platforms
- APIs
- Natural LanguageProcessing (NLP)
- Large Language

#### Models

- Generative Al
- Robotic Process Automation

## **SUMMARY**

Technical project manager seeks new role in similar field. Open to a wide range of positions, including (but not limited to) technical and non-technical management, business and data analysis, and machine learning. Previous experience in project management, tech development, and seed-stage ventures.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Cloud & Custom Applications Consultant – Capgemini US

June 2022 - Present

### **Integrations Business Analyst:**

- Evaluated 6 cloud solutions for client's transformation needs.
- Conducted in-depth analysis of business bottlenecks and legacy software tools across 2 engagements.
- Developed 6 requirement documents outlining technical specifications, including error handling, monitoring, and data warehousing requirements.

## Data Analyst:

- Documented client's software requirements across 200+ applications for cloud migration.
- Cleaned and structured data for use in 3 of Capgemini's internal data analysis tools.

# Scrum Master (Project Manager):

- Facilitated Scrum practices for 2 of client's machine learning team, overseeing a total of 20 developers.
- Achieved 110% velocity measured by Microsoft Azure Dashboards and Queries.

# Data Analyst Intern – NYU Entrepreneurial Institute

Sept. 2019 - May 2022

- Analyzed 5 years of aggregate data across 50+ Institute events by creating a behavioral network.
- Organized entrepreneurship events, such as start-up incubators and venture capital pitch-fests.

# **PROJECTS**

# Network Analysis (GitHub Link)

- Created 6 behavioral networks from event data for NYU's Entrepreneurial Institute.
- Gained experience with Python's Pandas and Sci-Kit Learn modules.

## Movie Review Sentiment Analysis (GitHub Link)

Calculated positive and negative sentiment for 50,000
IMDb movie reviews using a linear regression model.